# Sreelatha Vallabhaneni

# Full-Stack Web Developer, Front end Developer, React Native Developer and Software Tester

I am an energetic and imaginative web and Mobile app developer, passionate about creating user friendly and responsive applications while being motivated to learn new technologies at a fast pace. proven experience and success working as a software test engineer as an individual and team member. comprehensive talents across the design development, testing, debugging and documentation of applications.



- xreelatha.vallabhaneni@gmail.com
- Høje-Taastrup, Denmark
- in linkedin.com/in/sreelatha-vallabhaneni-37a406b9
- □ 71665956
- sreelatha-portfolio.netlify.app/
- github.com/Sreelatha-Vallabhaneni

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **DEVELOPER EXPERIENCE**

# React Native Developer (Self Project)

05/2021 - Present

#### Tasks

Developing a Music App for mobiles both IOS and Android, It's
a simple, innovative and user friendly app for users. Created
boiler plate code and currently developing reusable
components for screens, checking the output using
simulators / emulators and mobile devices. Currently using
React Native, Xcode, Android Studio, JavaScript, NPM, styled
components, Tailwind CSS, styleSheet, Hooks, etc..

### **React Native Developer**

Freetrailer

03/2021 - 03/2021

Copenhagen, Denmark.

Technical Stack

 React Native, Xcode, Android Studio, TypeScript, JavaScript, NodeJS, Hooks, Context, REST API, Git, BitBucket, etc....

# Frontend Developer winefamly

09/2020 - 11/2020

Copenhagen, Denmark

#### Tasks

 Connected React JS to Magento 2, developed some parts (like Add to cart, productList, Product Rate, Comments / Reviews, etc ...) in website with ReactJS to improve the speed, used webPackage, NPM, and reduced bundle size, Adding Widgets in Magento admin, Fixed Responsive styling, Participated in Daily / weekly meetings (Fx: Daily-Task, Task Grooming, stand-up, company Info, etc ...), etc ...

### **Full-Stack Web Developer**

HackYourFuture - Copenhagen

08/2019 - 05/2020 Copenhagen, Denmark

# Software Tester

Mavininfotech

Hyderabad, India

## Software Tester LiveTech

Tryderabad, ma

# **SKILLS**



# FINAL PROJECT

Dashboard App (seasony.dk). (2020) 🛂

 Developed a Dashboard App for visualizing sensor data from plants and a collaboration between HackYourFuture-CPH and seasony.dk, which is a startup specializing in vertical farming with robotics. It is Full-Stack application using ReactJS, Hooks, Storybook, Swagger for API documentation, NodeJS, KnexJS, MYSQL, ESLint, Prettier, Recharts, Firebase, Git, Github, Heroku etc...

## **EDUCATION**

Masters (M.Sc) in Signal Processing (2010 - 2012)

Blekinge Institute of Technology (Karlskrona, Sweden)

Bachelors (B.Tech) in Electronics (2005 - 2009)

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University. (Kakinada, India)

## **LANGUAGES**

Telugu English
Native or Bilingual Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

Danish Swedish

Limited Working Proficiency Elementary Proficiency

03/2013 - 03/2014 Hyderabad, India